# ERICA ER

Student



## PROFILE

As a fresh graduate with a diploma of Audio-Visual Technology from Ngee Ann Polytechnic, I am equipped with a strong set of knowledge, skills, experience, and competencies in this industry. I possess technical capacity in audio and visual technology, production and post-production. Being a creative individual, I enjoy cooperating in a team to provide brand new ideas. My vibrant, outgoing and enthusiastic personality will definitely be valuable asset to your organization.

## CONTACT



#### Phone

+65 9822 3792



## **Email**

mcer@hotmail.com



#### Address

Blk 658 Choa Chu Kang Crescent #06-63 Singapore 680658



## Web

yuiqnim.github.io/yuiqnim-website.github.io/

## EXPERIENCE

## Aug 2018 - Jan 2019

Design and Marketing Intern Three Star Brand

- · Design new series of product packaging
- · Assist in customer acquisition strategy

#### March 2017 - Aug 2017

Production Services Intern NUS Centre for the Arts

 Responsible for daily attendance and monthly payment of part-timers

## Dec 2014 - Jul 2018

Retail Assistant

Link Millennium Pte Ltd

- Responsible for the promotion and sale of retail products at the store
- Handled the cash register, ensuring the day's taking reconciled with purchases made

# EDUCATION

#### Apr 2015 - May 2018

Ngee Ann Polytechnic Graduated with a Diploma with Merit in Audio-Visual Technology

• GPA: 3.75

#### Jan 2011 - Dec 2014

Bukit View Secondary School Successfully completed the Cambridge GCE 'O' Level with a L1R4 score of 15 points

## SKILLS





